<feedbacks>
    <feedback>
        <userImage>u1.jpg</userImage>
        <userName>Nathaniel Hayes</userName>
        <rating>5</rating>
        <comment>I started with zero knowledge, and now I'm confidently conversing in Spanish! The lessons are engaging, and the progression is seamless. Grateful for this incredible language learning platform!</comment>
    </feedback>
    <feedback>
        <userImage>u2.jpg</userImage>
        <userName>Julian Thompson</userName>
        <rating>4</rating>
        <comment>Connecting with learners worldwide has been a highlight. The discussion forums and collaborative exercises create a sense of community. It's not just about language; it's about shared experiences and global connections.</comment>
    </feedback>
    <feedback>
        <userImage>u3.jpg</userImage>
        <userName>Amelia Carter</userName>
        <rating>5</rating>
        <comment>Responsive Support: Had a query? The support team is lightning-fast! They genuinely care about your progress and are quick to assist. It's reassuring to know they're there to help you every step of
            the way.</comment>
    </feedback>
    <feedback>
        <userImage>u4.jpg</userImage>
        <userName>Dominic Collins</userName>
        <rating>5</rating>
        <comment>User-Friendly Brilliance: As someone with a hectic schedule, I appreciate the user-friendly interface. Lessons are bite-sized, making it easy to fit learning into my daily routine. Plus, 
            the app adapts to my pace - it's like having a personal language tutor! Highly recommend.</comment>
    </feedback>
    <feedback>
        <userImage>u5.jpg</userImage>
        <userName>Sophia Turner</userName>
        <rating>5</rating>
        <comment>Game-changer: As a busy professional, this language learning platform has been a game-changer. It enables me to practice efficiently, and its convenience allows me to make the most of my 
            limited time.</comment>
    </feedback>
    <feedback>
        <userImage>u6.jpg</userImage>
        <userName>Isabella Mitchell</userName>
        <rating>4</rating>
        <comment>Cultural Immersion Delight: Beyond just learning words, this platform immerses you in the culture. Interactive exercises, real-life scenarios, and diverse content make the journey 
            enjoyable. I'm not just learning a language; I'm living it.</comment>
    </feedback>
</feedbacks>
